# LOW SAELEE

Oakland, California 94601 lowsaelee@gmail.com 510-935-8280

# **PROFILE**

Hardworking and expert computer technician with an A+ CompTIA and a Network+ CompTIA certificate specializing in Windows environment. 10 years of experience working as a computer technician with 6 years in education industry and 4 years in healthcare industry.

#### WORK HISTORY

IT Technician Level II, San Lorenzo Unified School District, 7/2014 – present (San Lorenzo, California)

- Image computers with Windows Deployment Services
- Implement Windows 10 migration
- Setup, troubleshoot and maintain computers for a high school and an elementary school site
- Manage Group Policy Objects for various OUs within the assigned school site
- Deploy software and printers using Group Policy
- First level troubleshooting with SMARTBoard technologies
- Setup and install network printers onto servers
- Install UPS batteries on server racks
- Manage accounts for Google Apps For Education
- Deployand troubleshoot Chromebooks and Nexus tablets
- Create and manage user accounts in Active Directory
- Create custom list forms with InfoPath for SharePoint
- Create custom workflows with SharePoint Designer for SharePoint
- Create custom workflows with Microsoft Flow and Power Automate
- Train teachers on the use of productivity software such as G Suite and MS Office
- Use helpdesk ticketing system to communicate and update ticket issues

# PC Maintenance Technician, LifeLong Medical Care, 11/2010 – 6/2014 (Berkeley, California)

- Setup computers; install/uninstall programs, replace computer parts
- Supported 700+ users via phone, VNC, DameWare, Remote Desktop Services and in person
- Supported both Windows XP and Windows 7 OS
- Managed cell phone new orders, replacements, and inventory
- Troubleshoot cell phones
- Configured, maintained, and inventoried printers/copiers
- Assisted with basic network monitoring, configuration, and repair
- Used Active Directory to manage user information
- Ordered printers from contracted vendor
- Ordered computer equipment from CDWG.com
- Helped answer questions regarding Microsoft suite and other software used by company
- Helped with implementation and troubleshoot NextGen EHR and EPM
- Installed, tested and troubleshoot vitals and EKG machines for NextGen
- Managed SharePoint intranet
- Developed SharePoint workflows using SharePoint Designer
- Managed user information on PBX phone system
- Cross-connected 66 blocks
- Managed Chromebooks

• Wrote scripts in DOS for managing computers and obtaining inventory information

# **EDUCATION**

University of California, Davis – Bachelor's Degree in Economics and Chinese

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

CompTIA A+, CompTIA Network+

# **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office, SharePoint, Active Directory, Group Policy, DOS scripting, printer/copiers, Linux, GIMP, Audacity, Android Studio

# LANGUAGES BEYOND ENGLISH

Fluent Iu Mien - Native Language (read, write, speak) Advance Mandarin Chinese (read, write, speak) Basic Thai (read, write, speak)

#### **PROJECT**

LearnMien.com 2014-present

- Built web server with LAMP stack in virtual environment with Oracle VirtualBox
- Built and maintain MySQL database
- Manage backups of virtual machine with Bash scripts
- Back up files and database
- Use Bootstrap framework with HTML, CSS and JavaScript for frontend development
- Use PHP with MySQL for the backend development
- Build HTML5 games
- Design logos and graphics with GIMP
- Create lessons for learning the Mien language
- Designed and built a dictionary database for querying words
- Record and edit audio using Audacity
- Built apps for Android devices with Android Studio
- Translated website to both Thai and Chinese language